taxback.com 2015-03-23

# Privacy Policy | Taxback.com Protects Your Personal Information

This privacy policy sets out how taxback.com uses and protects any information you give when you use this website. Taxback.com is fully committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.   
Taxback.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 31 July 2013.

 **What information we collect**  
We may collect the following personal information from you:

  *  Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  *  All Financial Information pertinent to filling a tax return on your behalf 
  *  Social Security Number or equivalent, depending on your tax country of residence
  *  Demographic information such as age, education, gender, interests and zip code

 **How your information is used**  
We require this information to understand your needs, to provide you with a better service and in particular for the following reasons: 

  *  To administer your account
  *  To send you periodical marketing and promotional communications, such as emails, newsletters, SMS text messages
  *  To provide the service you have requested
  *  We may use the information to improve our products and services
  *  We will never sell your information

 **Choice/Opt-Out**  
You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails.

 **Tell-A-Friend**  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Taxback.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.  
Your friend may contact us at [ infotaf@taxback.com](mailto:infotaf@taxback.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.  
As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

 **Information Obtained from Third Parties**  
If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

 **Information Sharing**  
We will not share your personal information with third parties unless we have your prior consent to do so or unless we are required to do so by law to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.  
We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us deliver our service, such as shipping documents to you. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.  
We may also disclose your personal information when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.   
If taxback.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.  
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the address below. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. If you decide to become a client of taxback.com and you store personal information online with us, then you can log into your account at anytime and update your personal information.

**Cookies and other Tracking Technologies**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer hard drive. Cookies help analyse web traffic and allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. For more information about our cookies policy, click [here](https://www.taxback.com/en/cookies-policy/).

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

We use cookies, pixels and tracking technologies on this site. We link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You can choose to accept or decline cookies (see ‘How can you manage your cookie preferences?’ below). Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However this may prevent you from accessing certain functions on taxback.com.

Some of our business partners or third parties use cookies, pixels or other tracking technologies on our site. Data is only collected in the aggregate. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

 ** _How can you manage your cookie preferences?_**

Using your browser settings in, for example, Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari or Chrome, you can set which cookies to accept and which to reject. Where you find these settings depends on which browser you use. If you are unsure, use the "Help" function in your browser to locate the settings you need.  
If you choose not to accept certain cookies, our website may not work properly.

 ** _Remarketing & Analytics_**

We currently use remarketing as an online advertising strategy. This means that after visiting our website, you may see our adverts on third party sites across the internet. These third party vendors use cookies in order to display our adverts. 

In order to do this, Google collects data about your activities that does not personally or directly identify you when you visit our website. This information may include the content you view, the date and time that you view this content, the products you purchase, or your location information associated with your IP address. We use the information we collect to provide you with more relevant advertisements. 

Any data used to serve targeted advertisements is de-identified and is not used to personally or directly identify you.

To help us create a better and more tailored service for you, we are currently using Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. This tool uses a first-party cookie. You can opt out of Google tracking at any time by adjusting your choices in Google’s [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads) or learn more about online behavioural advertising [here](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers).

**Additional Policy Information**  
Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. We also have testimonials on our sites, for which if a user posted personal information with this, we have received permission.

 **Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**  
We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

 **Contact Information**  
You can contact us by writing or email us at the address below:  
Taxback.com European Headquarters  
IDA Business & Technology Park  
Ring Road  
Kilkenny  
Ireland

Taxback.com US Headquarters  
333 N. Michigan Ave  
Suite 2415  
Chicago 60601 IL  
USA  
Tel: +353 1 887 1999

Free phone (from Ireland): 1800 99 18 05  
Fax: +353 1 670 6963  
Email: [info@taxback.com](mailto:info@taxback.com).
